[Characters, behaviors, places, organizations,
professions, or events shown in the series
are entirely fictional,
solely for the purpose of entertainment,
with no intention to instruct
or promote any kind of behavior;
viewer discretion is advised]
I made you breakfast.
When afflictions come your way,
even I cannot come to your rescue.
Never.
Dear vital spirits.
My dearest,
stay here with me.
Cursed with black magic...
[Been put under a love spell]
[The signs of being under a love spell,
or Ya Faed charm,
can be seen through
significant changes
in behavior and emotion]
[For Saneh Ya Faed, beware of food]
At the station...
I was just going to wake you up.
Where are you rushing off to?
Come here.
I woke up before daybreak to cook.
No, I'm fine, thanks.
I already told you
I don't eat breakfast.
Just have a taste.
I'm good.
It'll be such a waste.
What you yourself cook
is never as delightful
as when someone cooks with you in mind.
Very well, then.
I will make you coffee.
I'd rather not.
I'll find something
to drink near the station.
I don't wanna bother you.
Had those words not come from
someone with whom I shared a bed,
I would have thought
you found me abhorrent.
It's...
It's not like that.
I just...
don't usually eat...
Be it lunch or an afternoon meal,
as you wish, Officer.
I do not usually dine at supper,
but I shall prepare a meal set for you.
♫Along with ghostly spirits
hounding relentlessly,♫
♫May the maras be ravaged
and perish completely♫
♫Vindictive spirits, tyrannical psyches,♫
♫Meant to betray, slaughter, and invade,♫
♫Were any souls to brush
against my karmic soulmate,♫
♫They shall bury the thought
of returning to their realm♫
♫With incantation and virtue as shield,♫
♫At my feet,
they shall surrender and kneel,♫
♫Chanting, "Sadhu," of their own will♫
The suspects?
Exactly.
Tons.
"Be it lunch or an afternoon meal,"
"as you wish, Officer."
Oh,
the premium tiffin is back.
If you wanna eat it, feel free to take it.
It's all yours.
Won't your partner get mad?
You should really use these bait questions
during investigations.
I think...
you'll get a promotion in no time.
Oh, that mouth.
I'll take it, ma'am.
Alright.
Feel free to eat it if you're hungry.
What's on the menu today?
Oh...
Oh!
There are grapes, too.
Wow...
These are hard to come by.
Mm!
Scrumptious, Lieutenant.
Sarge,
can I ask you something?
Yes, ma'am.
Being cursed with black magic...
or the dark arts,
that...is real, right?
It exists.
There was a man from the Northeast
who got so hung up on a woman here
that he transferred here for work
and never left.
Really, Sarge?
Really.
Who is he?
That's me.
Take it from my wife,
who got the great charm of metta and favor
tattooed by the Master.
Nowadays, we still
go at it hard after work.
Be serious.
I'm not freaking kidding, Sarge.
I mean,
superstars get tattoos from her, too.
She has tons of disciples.
If you're interested,
I can ask my wife to pull some strings.
I'd rather not, Sarge.
I think...
I'm good with what I have.
Though...
what I'm curious about is...
she has that many disciples,
and each of them
is a famous superstar or actress.
That means
she must have made a lot from ritual fees.
That's why she could build
such a ginormous house, right?
Don't say things like that, Lieutenant.
With her,
if you ask about a ritual fee
or her pay,
she gets real angry.
She's been doing it
since her father's time.
She's helped both the rich and the poor.
Otherwise, she'd be a billionaire.
Mm.
My wife asked
if you didn't spend
the night at the residence.
She knocked for a long time.
Ah, it's okay.
I get it.
Everyone who comes to
the police quarters sees it.
Do you have any accommodations
you can recommend?
I want the one with
a three- or six-month lease.
I have some.
Let me finish this first.
Your partner did a great job.
Not my partner.
I don't have a partner.
You don't?
Serves you right.
Just stay single.
Sorry, ma'am.
Thank you so much, Master.
How is the child?
She's doing better,
but we're letting her stay on leave
until she's mentally ready to come back.
She may have a fever or body aches.
Give her some medicine
and tell her to rest.
She will return to
her normal self within three days.
Yes, Master.
Thank you very much again, Master.
I'll go tell her guardians right away
to put their minds at ease.
On the day of the incident,
the lieutenant merely did
what a good officer ought to.
Do not hold it against her.
Yes, Master.
People have been talking on and on
about this new policewoman.
But if you, Master, insist,
I'm relieved.
I myself do not hold it against her.
Hence, others should not.
We must also thank her for her courage.
Do you understand
what I am saying, Miss?
I do.
In fact...
the child's mother asked me
to thank the officer on her behalf.
Though I
haven't had time to stop by the station.
I was going to give her stuff back.
Whatever of hers is dropped here
or anywhere hereafter,
leave it only in my care.
Oh, yes.
Hello.
Do you have a room for monthly rent?
Let me check for you, ma'am.
Hello, Sarge.
How's it going, Lieutenant?
Did you get a room?
That place is the best in the district.
I'm waiting for the staff
to take a look, Sarge.
I'm sorry, but we have no vacancies.
- It's okay. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Thank you.
There goes the first one, Sarge.
There's a dog here?
Hello.
Hello, beautiful.
I'm looking for a monthly rental.
Give me a sec.
Hello?
Huh!
The water isn't running, the power is out,
and the A/C's not cooling?
I'll send our guy to take care of it.
It'll take just a sec.
Alright.
Alright, alright.
You were saying?
The water isn't running well?
It's crystal clear. No worries.
It runs every day.
And the A/C isn't cooling well?
Again, no worries. Every room
is nice and cold. Down to 18 degrees.
You seem to be
breaking out in a sweat there.
This is normal.
Hello, Sarge.
This place...
doesn't really work.
The staff seems weirdly confused.
The A/Cs aren't even doing anything.
He's real confused, the staff here.
He's eating rice with limes!
Feel free to take a look.
- So if I want to sign a lease...
- Hold on, hold on a sec.
Hi there.
Who is this?
Oh... Ooh!
You're confirming and paying the deposit?
Sure thing. Okay.
Sure thing. See you.
Alrighty.
If I'm ready to sign a lease here...
We're fully booked!
But if you're interested
in reserving a room,
you can wire me the deposit in advance.
Where's your ID card?
If you wire the money to my account,
I'll lower the rent to 500 baht.
From 10,000, so think carefully.
Think!
Just think. Wire it to my account. It's...
Though...what do you do for a living?
I'm a cop.
A what now?
A cop.
Just wire it to
this place's account, then, sweetie.
You seem friendly, Auntie.
I am friendly, sweetie.
Friendly for a swindle, that is.
Huh? A swind-what?
Hello, it's Plaifah again today,
along with my friend.
What's your name again?
My name is Book.
Let's read your comments.
They're saying I'm prettier
than you, that's it.
Not true.
[Grilled Pork Station]
- Guys, let's not lie to her.
- Uh...
Don't get her hopes up.
Auntie, I'd like three chicken skewers.
Girl, look.
What is this one, Auntie?
- Grilled marinated pork.
- Oh, pork.
What's your name?
Can I have your Insta?
I'm not on social media.
Then, your number, please!
Pwease, pwease, pwease.
I don't just give my number out to anyone.
You're playing hard to get.
Good!
Someone who's hard to win over
is just my type!
- Let go.
- No, I won't.
- Kid, let go.
- As if I'd let go of someone so slick.
Hey...what are you girls doing?
Oh,
we're going live, creating some content.
I'm Plaifah.
What's your name?
Priew!
Your darling commented that
you're making
a fool out of her by cheating.
Since when did I do that?
She was born a fool.
Stephan,
you dumbass!
I've never made a fool out of you
because you
have always been one!
And this...
is my new girl!
She's...
What is your name?
Peem.
She's Peem!
She looks good,
has a nice body,
and her skin is so fair!
She looks like she takes 10 showers a day.
Someone like you
could never compare.
All you do is ride a motorcycle all day,
revving and revving.
Not fabulous!
Are you done now?
- If you are, please let go.
- No, I'm not letting go!
I still want to talk to you, Peem.
Hey, Miss!
Let go of my girl right now.
Don't say I didn't warn ya!
Who's your girl?!
I already broke up with you this morning.
And this is my new girl!
That doesn't freaking count!
I freaking warned ya!
Let go of her.
I'm not holding her.
There, you're doing it.
Pointing fingers, huh?
If you're just bickering, be my guest.
But if you're gonna fight,
good!
I'm taking you all in
for an attitude adjustment.
Are you a teacher?
I'm not a teacher.
Oh, what are you?
A "cop."
Whoa!
My dad's a cop too, just so you know.
There's no way
I'm letting you slip through
my fingers that easily.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ugh, Stephan, let go! Let go!
So you're not listening
to a word I'm saying?
Why is an outsider
sticking her nose in?!
This is between...
Ow, ow!
Ow!
That was crisp.
Totally my type.
My first time feeling like a bottom.
What's the matter?
I'm a bottom, that's what.
So cute!
What a boss!
And you modded your motorcycle.
Do you know it's against the law
to modify a vehicle?
Good.
You'll get fined at the station.
Miss...
Don't fine me.
Please don't fine me.
I'm so sorry, Miss.
Please don't do anything to me.
I'm just a cute, wittle baby.
Please don't.
Please give her some grace.
- She doesn't have a dime.
- Mm.
She's spent all the money
modding the motorcycle.
Just help her.
Please?
For her red hair's sake.
Please, Peem?
Sure.
Sergeant, go.
- You said you weren't gonna arrest me!
- Stephan!
Stephan!
Miss!
How am I gonna go home?
Could you give me a ride home?
Please?
Why didn't you call
your guardians to do that?
Whoa...
If I call them,
I'll never hear the end of it.
I'm not doing that.
Give me a ride home, please.
Give me directions. I'll give you a ride.
How cute!
Oh, whoa... Damn it.
- Priew!
- We can give you a ride!
What? I'm going with Peem!
- What? How could you just dump us?!
- I'm going with Peem!
Get lost!
Thank you so much, Peem,
for giving me a ride.
And...
someone's home, right?
My parents are probably inside.
I'm not so sure.
Can I go home with you?
I'd rather not, Priew.
By the way...
speaking of the motorcycle,
can you pass the message along
to your girlfriend
that if she behaves herself
and...
promises me
she'll reverse the modifications,
I'll return the motorcycle to her.
As for the fine,
I'll...
have a word with your guardians later.
If you behave yourself,
I won't fine you.
Understood?
Okay, okay!
Then...wait here for a bit.
I'll call my dad for you.
Just a second!
Dad!
Dad, open the door for me!
Are you home?!
Dad!
- I'm here!
- Ooh...
Whoa, Sarge!
Oh?
What are you doing here, Lieutenant?
Is she...your daughter?
She is.
My daughter.
And why are you out here?
- I can't get inside, sweetie.
- What?
Why can't you?!
I'm busted, sweetie.
- Ugh, just stop...
- Sarge, do you know
what a troublemaker she's been?
Tell me about it later.
Lieutenant...
please call my wife over to help.
I wanna get inside.
Why don't you call her yourself?
She won't... She won't open the door.
Please help us. I wanna get inside.
- Go all out, Lieutenant.
- Want some?
- Consider it a welcome dinner.
My hubby told me
you've been feeding him.
- He's been well-fed for two days now
- You want anything?
Thank you. Please eat a ton today.
Come on.
I'm the one who should be thanking him.
- Get this, I just transferred here.
- Eat some veggies...
There are still so many things
I have to get used to.
I'm lucky to have him.
Otherwise,
I'd be in a really tough spot.
When I first moved here,
I was just like you.
But someone helped me adapt.
- Wear some nice PJ tonight.
- Ugh!
At this age,
you don't have to be so lovey-dovey.
It's okay to take it down a notch.
I'm so tired of raising this one.
I'm the only one raising him.
You're always out and about.
Never once have you given me a hand.
Damn you...Priew!
Priew...
What?
You told me your name was Plaifah.
Well, my name's Plaifah.
Good grief!
"Plaifah," my foot, Lieutenant.
This girl's damn name is Priew!
When I was pregnant,
I always craved limes,
mangoes, and all that sour stuff,
so I named her "Priew," which means "sour."
That's not true, Lieutenant.
I'm still Plaifah.
Don't believe her.
Priew.
Mom!
And you,
don't be so slutty.
People are gonna say
your dad didn't discipline you!
I am,
but she wouldn't listen.
Well, get it through her thick skull!
- Discipline her until she listens!
- Ugh...
Stop, stop, stop.
It's genetic, you know?
Like mother,
like daughter, Mommy.
- Don't badmouth my wifey.
- This kid!
Deal with her!
Do it. Now!
Oh, I'll do it to you tonight.
Do what?
- You'll definitely get some.
- Peem, want me to feed you?
Do what?
- Our third kid is on the way.
- I'm good.
Darling...
Okay, I'll go shower while I wait.
Props,
get up, sweetie. Go on.
- Yeah, I'll give it to you hard.
- Cover your ears, cover your ears.
I'll slam it like, "Bam, bam, bam, bam."
Jeez, I'm not getting any sleep that way.
I'll make sure you can't walk.
- Kiddos,
- Go on. Let me put on my shoes first.
if you hear anything tonight,
don't get curious.
Ugh!
Hey,
don't you feel
protective of your daughter?
She's a young girl.
Look how short her shorts were,
not to mention how late she gets home.
I'm...
not protective, but I sure am worried.
With that faux-hawk butch of hers,
they fight every day.
Though...
they always get back together.
They...
can never truly let each other go.
The reason...
they can't do that
might be because...
they're a safe space
for each other.
Otherwise...
they wouldn't keep
coming back to each other.
Right, Sarge.
Can I ask you a question?
Why...
did you decide to move to Phop Phra?
I've transferred to many locations.
I...was a stray.
I had nowhere to settle,
so I built my own family here.
I think sometimes,
it's about having a safe space,
like you said.
A place called home.
But a home isn't just a place.
It's where...
the people who love you,
and the people you love,
are waiting.
I suspect
you're asking this because
you've started
to take a liking to someone here?
Aha!
There's no one, Sarge.
Eat your food.
Is there no one,
or are you just not sure?
Who are you into?
Who?
Who's the lucky one?
No one!
Anyway, where are you
gonna spend the night?
Sarge.
Yes?
Pass me the beer.
What?
You said you didn't drink, though.
Well...
I changed my mind.
- Oh...
- Come on.
Who are you seeing?
Are you meeting someone after this?
Ooh...
Aha, so flustered you can't open the can.
There.
Suspish.
Cheers, Sarge.
Bottoms up.
You're gonna get it hard.
Who's the one?
Why are you downing it so fast?
In a hurry?
I'm just teasing ya.
If I drink that fast,
Priew's mama is gonna get some.
We'll rock all four bed legs.
It's gonna sound like
a real slaughterhouse.
If you walk past my room,
someone will be crying out to God,
even though we're not Christians.
Not asking you to pitch in more than 500.
You've already downed all my beers.
Hey,
are you mad at me about this morning?
Hm?
You're not answering.
I was...
just unsure.
Seek your bed, Lieutenant.
It is well into the night.
Are you avoiding me on purpose?
Huh?
Someone like myself does not avoid others,
but I cannot share a bed
with someone who is intoxicated,
nor can I bind my life
to someone of different morals.
I do not wish
to hold you against your will.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think that...
something like this
would hurt you this much.
I'm sorry.
I love;
therefore, I am troubled.
Mortal or immortal,
I do not wish for anyone
to brush against you.
I yearn for you to be mine alone to claim.
As for me,
I remain unpledged to anyone,
lingering to be claimed
by my lover.
Well, well, well.
- Are you...
- We will talk tomorrow.
Seek a good night's rest.
I will sleep in the prayer room.
What?
That's a total miss.
My spit flew out.
She didn't even finish wiping me down.
All I did was skip breakfast with her.
Is she really that furious?
What do you want?
Bullets.
I need bullets
that can stop invulnerable criminals
with impenetrable skin,
the kind who practice
black magic like you do.
[Treatise on War: Great Weapons of War]
[Bullet Consecration Ritual]
[Consecration Materials]
I'm late.
Mm.
She's probably back at her sanctum.
Just have a taste.
I'm good.
It'll be such a waste.
My dearest,
stay here with me.
I will request the officer on duty
to summarize the case file
and send it over ASAP.
This case is quite sensitive.
Of course.
I'd like the evidence to be more solid.
Sure.
I'll send it over ASAP.
What are these photos?
These photos confirm clues about Krating.
Right now, the guy
is hiding out in Mae Sot.
So why haven't you
told me about this, sir?
I have no obligation to report
this matter to my subordinates.
Besides, this matter
is outside our jurisdiction.
Let Mae Sot Police Station handle it.
But I'm here for this case.
You know that.
All I know is that
you can't be harmed,
so do as I say.
Let the local police
handle this matter.
If you're done here, be on your way.
Oh.
How are you, Lieutenant?
Where did you sleep last night?
Huh?
Lieutenant, what's the matter?
Lieutenant, Lieutenant.
Calm down.
Take it easy, Lieutenant.
What's going on?
The chief knew about the clues
and kept them from me, Sarge.
He doesn't want me
to investigate the case.
What does that mean?
My family urged him
to make sure I stayed safe.
But I came here specifically
to investigate the case, Sarge.
I know that well.
So what are you gonna do next?
I'm going to Mae Sot.
You're well-versed in the area, right?
Wanna come with?
I'm not that well-versed.
But at least you know the area
better than I do.
So what are you gonna say?
Are you coming or not?
Fine, I'm coming.
[Mae Sot, Tak]
Hello.
- Hello, Auntie.
- Uh...
May I ask you some questions?
Have you seen, uh...
a man around...
170 cm tall.
He's a little tanned and sturdy.
Have you seen him?
I don't think so.
Hello.
Have you seen a man around 170 cm tall?
Uh, never.
Sarge.
Yes?
I see a security camera there.
There's one.
Yes, ma'am.
I will liaise with Mae Sot Police Station.
- Please do, Sarge.
- Yes, ma'am.
Let's have a meal now.
The khao soi place over there is amazing.
- Wanna go?
- Is it?
Delicious food.
Ordered three bowls just for myself.
That's to freshen you up.
Thank you, Sarge.
Are you tired, Sarge?
All day,
you've been drinking water nonstop.
I'm hungover.
After you left last night,
I chugged two to two
and a half bottle on my own.
Though
drinking tons of water
can help flush the alcohol out.
Can that really
help flush the alcohol out, Sarge?
What?
When you pee,
it might just get diluted.
Someone like myself does not avoid others,
but I cannot share a bed
with someone who is intoxicated,
nor can I bind my life
to someone of different morals.
Right.
From...
what you've told me,
I happen to know someone
who can reach out to officers
at Mae Sot Police Station.
Do you remember Chai,
the guy who brought me desserts
at the municipal market?
I do.
Chai's nephew is a police inspector
at Mae Sot Police Station.
I think if he has any clues,
he'll probably send them to you.
That'd be great.
However,
the chief can't find out about this
until we know for sure...
that we can access them.
Yes, ma'am.
Ugh...
Jeez,
I'm hungry!
When will we ever get to eat?
Coming, officers.
Jeez!
Jeez, how impatient of you.
We put in our order half an hour ago.
Yes, your food is ready.
This is made with a special recipe.
- What recipe?
- Right.
Uh...
It's chicken khao soi
for those who like to khao-slam at night.
- Mm.
- Yeah, just go if you can't crack a joke.
Right.
Whenever I eat this, I think of my mom
because she does it better.
Right.
Give it a try, Lieutenant. It's tasty.
Sarge,
so many actors
have visited this shop, though.
They take photos of everyone who comes in.
It's just to promote the shop.
Sarge,
please liaise with them
for security footage
dating back two to three days, and...
also get footage from the stores
and the neighborhood around here.
Yes, ma'am. I'll get right to it.
And if possible...
I'd like to get to know Inspector Chon,
Chai's nephew you mentioned.
Could you ask him to meet me?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you so much
for always helping me, Sarge.
If something happens in the future,
I promise I'll take full responsibility.
I admire what a ball of fire you are,
so tenacious about this case.
But I do want you to understand
that your life should be your priority.
And I don't want you to think...
that a life for a life
is the right way to go.
Thank you for your concern, Sarge.
I think
we could still make it
in time if we leave now.
Where to?
To the Master's sanctum, of course.
If we leave now for Phop Phra,
the sanctum should still be open.
So why are we...
going to her sanctum?
Good grief.
You told me
you were interested in the great charm,
so I asked my wife to book an appointment.
You've got it all wrong, Sarge.
I'm not looking to get anything done.
The reason I asked you
is just to get some general information.
Aha.
Let's just go.
It's already been booked, anyway.
Just go and meet her for once,
or else I'll lose face.
Come on, get in the car.
Come on!
Chop-chop.
Sarge!
- Come on.
- If you wanna go, go by yourself.
Nah!
Lieutenant.
Wrong car, Sarge!
Open the door, Lieutenant.
Why aren't you driving?
I'm too lazy to drive, Lieutenant.
I'll be going now, Master.
Lieutenant.
Go to her.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not afraid, Sarge.
I'm not looking to get anything done.
I'm just accompanying you.
What?
Go on. You're already here, anyway.
You have arrived at my sanctum.
How could you depart empty-handed?
Come.
Let me incant a verse upon you,
and you can decide then.
Go.
- What?
- Alright, Sarge.
Go now.
Whatever clouded your mind,
has it been warded off by the alcohol?
I won't cause you trouble
like I did last night.
Come.
Let me see your face up close.
Closer.
Know you of the Sattabut lotus?
Pray you, take your leave.
The ritual I shall perform
upon the lieutenant
will last long.
Since you scorn these rituals,
I have never thought
to trouble you with one.
For someone like me,
should I wish to have anyone
enamored of me,
my beauty alone
would suffice...
At every sunrise and nightfall,
I yearn for you, my dearest.
That is why last night was such a torment
Do you not feel as I do?
Then, we should spend the night together.
Let me be the one to pleasure you
until I ease what torments you.
What you need, my dearest,
is not something
that may be done with ease.
Perils will come your way
from the very instant
you seek the sacred materials.
I'm not afraid of evil.
Should you be determined
to make consecrated bullets,
always bear in mind the virtues
and faith in good deeds.
Though you do not hold them
close to your heart,
dare not desecrate them.
I'm here to uphold justice.
Though I can't let go of all my vengeance,
I would never want to
desecrate anyone's faith.
I have faith in
the teachings of Buddhism.
I pray that you
guide my good intentions
to success.
My dearest,
come to me.
Wear this upon you.
Do not give it to anyone so readily again.
May the sacred beings watch over you
until your good intentions
prevail.
Yes,
Master.
Do I have to call you...
"Master," like everyone else does?
You neither embrace
nor believe in what I am.
No need to address me as others do.
Then...
Thank you,
Master Bulan.
♫Mantra of love, please take the lead♫
♫So our hearts are sworn by♫
♫I shall love and commit♫
♫Until the day I die♫
♫As long as I shall breathe♫
♫I will be your karmic soulmate♫
♫Until my being fades♫
♫May sacred mantras bind us together♫
This is Inspector Chon,
stationed at Mae Sot Police Station.
From the clues I've gathered in secret,
Krating and his guys
are moving along
the Thailand-Myanmar border.
If the person
you're waiting for isn't me...
you can be honest.
As you gather the sacred materials,
the Buddha's virtues
shall spread far and wide.
Restless spirits and ghosts shall storm in.
♫It's not that I don't feel it♫
♫It's not that I'm cold-hearted♫
♫For the love you've given♫
♫It's because it feels too good to be true,♫
♫So much so that I doubt if it's true♫
♫If it's smoke and mirrors,
a dream that lingers♫
♫Deeply swayed by love,
all while shaken with dread,♫
♫Scared that it's not love
after all in the end♫
♫What if, between us,♫
♫It's nothing but a perfect illusion,♫
♫Nothing short of deception?♫
♫What I've kept hidden for ages,♫
♫Do you know how painful it is♫
♫To keep my heart locked away in a cage?♫
♫Can you so gently give me some time,♫
♫For me to ponder what's on my mind?♫
♫I would hate to be wavering
when love binds♫
♫Deeply swayed by love,
all while shaken with dread,♫
♫Scared that it's not love
after all in the end♫
♫What if, between us,♫
♫It's nothing but a perfect illusion,♫
♫Nothing short of deception?♫
♫What I've kept hidden for ages,♫
♫Do you know how painful it is♫
♫To keep my heart locked away in a cage?♫
♫Tell me it's not an illusion
you beautifully created♫
♫Don't let my heart suffer
and ache inside this cage♫
♫I would do anything just to escape♫
♫What if, between us,♫
♫It's nothing but a perfect illusion,♫
♫Nothing short of deception?♫
♫What I've kept hidden for ages,♫
♫Do you know how painful it is♫
♫To keep my heart locked away in a cage?♫
♫I don't want to lock my heart away♫
♫I wish you'd know one day♫